Woody Allen Papers, 1955-2012: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 5: Additions, 1955-2008; 16.0 boxes
  - Subseries 5A: Writings: Manuscripts, Screenplays and Essays, 1955-2008; 14.0 boxes
    - "Pinchuk's Law", 2006; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
      2 TMss with autograph corrections, 5 pp. each; TMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.; The New Yorker's proof with autograph corrections (facsimile), 5 pp. dated May 5, 2006.
    - "Playboy", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      TMs of theatrical sketch, 7 pp.
    - Play It Again, Sam, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
      TMs of play adaption to film with autograph corrections (misc. numbered pages); TMs of screenplay (Xerox), 64 pp.
    - Play it Again, Sam, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      TMs bound copy with autograph corrections. Act I (47 pp.), Act II (45 pp.), Act III (27 pp.) = 119 pp.
    - "The Practical Joke", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
      Unpublished short story TMs with one autograph correction, 11 pp.; TMs (Xerox), 11 pp.
    - "A Prestige Address", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
      TMS, 7 pp; TMs of a story, 7 pp. labeled "Final draft."
    - "The Psychic Wife", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      TMs, 16 pp.
    - "Psychological Warfare", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      TMs, 3 pp.
    - "The Pussycat Papers", 1965 June 27; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 4 pp.; TMss with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 and 6 pp.; original tear sheets from the New York Sunday Herald Tribune magazine.
    - "The Query", 1976-1977; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      TMs (Xerox), 8 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 7 pp.; original tear sheets from the Sept. 18, 1976 issue of The New Republic and the Feb. 11, 1977 edition of the Los Angeles Times.
    - "A Rainy Day in New York" (excerpts from an unproduced film), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      Mixture of AMs and TMs with autograph corrections of excerpts from an unproduced film.
    - "Random Reflections of a Second Rate Mind", 1989-1992; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 10 pp.; TMs labeled "First draft"; TMs with autograph corrections, 12 pp.; 4 TLSs between Allen and Michael Lerner, plus other business correspondence; tear sheets (Xerox) from Tikkun, Vol. 5, No. 1 (1990).
    - "Remembering Needleman", 1976; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 6 pp.; original tear sheets from the July 24, 1976 issue of The New Republic.
    - "Reminiscences: Places and People", 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      TMs, 6 pp.; The New Yorker's TMs copy with their autograph corrections, 6 pp. and related TL; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 pp.; original tear sheets from the Dec. 229, 1975 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "Report to America", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - "Rest in Peace of Mind", circa 1955; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      Unpublished TMs, 5 pp.
    - "Retribution", 1979; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
      TMs, 23 pp. and TLS of rejection from The New Yorker, AMs and TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox).
    - "Rhino-Wino", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
    - "Riverside Drive" (one-act play), 2003; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      TMs early draft with autograph corrections, approx. 41 pp.; TMs, 43 pp.
    - "Sam, You Made the Pants Too Fragrant", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
    - "The Scrolls", 1974-1984; portion of 1 folder (Folder 12)
      TMss (original and Xerox), 6 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 6 pp.; AMS (Xerox), 16 pp.; original tear sheets from the Aug. 31, 1974 issue of The New Republic.
    - "A Second Hand Memory" (two-act play), 2003 February 27-June; portion of more than 4 folders (Folder 13-15)
      This Off-Broadway play opened in November 2004.
      - Version 1, 2003 February 27; portion of 1 folder (Folder 12)
        TMss, 96 pp (2 copies)
      - Version 2, 2003 May-June; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 96 pp. May 7, 2003 printed on cover page and "Up To Date June 2003" handwritten at top right.
      - Version 3, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
        TMs, 94 pp.
    - "Selections from the Allen Notebooks", 1973-1976; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 pp. and misc. 3 pp.; original tear sheets from November 5, 1973 issue of The New Yorker; TL from their Fiction Department to Allen.
    - Series Outline, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 2 pp., and TMs (carbon), 3 pp., of Allen's proposal for a half hour television series.
    - "The Seven Deadly Arts" Synopsis, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs (carbon), 8 pp. (written on title page is "Seven Deadly Sins Synopsis")
    - "Sex," "Death" and "God" (3 one-act plays), undated; 1.0 folder
      Three plays comprising an evening of one-act plays.
      - "Sex", undated; portion of 1 folder (Folder 4)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 42 pp.; 2 TMss (same miscellaneous pages), one with autograph corrections and one without.
      - "God", undated; portion of 1 folder (Folder 4)
        2 TMss (same miscellaneous pages), one with autograph corrections and one without.
      - "Death", undated; portion of 1 folder (Folder 4)
        AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), unnumbered pages; 2 TMss (same miscellaneous pages), one with autograph corrections and one without. This was later made into the film Shadows and Fog (1991).
    - "The Shallowest Man", 1979-1996; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 10 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 13 pp., reprint from the Winter 1980 issue of The Kenyon Review; TL (rejection) from The New Yorker.
    - "Shindai", 1968-1969; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
      TMs (carbon), 3 pp.; TL and uncorrected proof from Playboy, and related correspondence
    - "Sing You Sacher Torts", 2002; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
      TMss (original and Xerox) with autograph corrections, 8 pp.; AMs, 6 pp.; The New Yorker's revisions #2 and #3 with autograph corrections, 6 pp., and related correspondence
    - "Slang Origins", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
      TMss (original and Xerox), 5 pp.
    - Small Time Crooks (2000 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 77 pp.
    - "Strung Out", 2003; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 4 pp.; TMs, 4 pp.; T he New Yorker's TMs proof with autograph corrections (facsimile), 4 pp.
    - "Surprise Divorce", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      TMs (Xerox), 3 pp.
    - "Surprise Party", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      TMs of a theatrical sketch from Broadway show, 4 pp.
    - Sweet and Lowdown (1999 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      TMs with autograph corrections of a cut-and-paste version that combines an old film script with new writing, 65 pp.
    - "Sweet Sixteen", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      TMs of TV sketch, 12 pp.
    - Take the Money and Run (1969 film): An Original Screenplay by Woody Allen and Mickey Rose, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      TMs (bound screenplay), 81 pp.
    - Take the Money and Run, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
      TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 13 pp.; AMs (Xerox), 6 pp.; 2 TMss (Xerox), 5 pp.; TMs of interview with Allen, 2 pp.
    - "Tandoori Ransom", 2000; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
      AMs, 9 pp.; TMss with autograph corrections, 7 pp. and 9 pp.
    - Television Documentary script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
      2 TMss (Xerox), 26 pp.
    - "Think?", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      TMs (carbon) of a script for a live thirty minnute comedy show, 24 pp.
    - "This Nib For Hire", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp., and miscellaneous TMs and AMs pages
    - Three One-Act Plays (book), 2003-2004; more than 4 folders (Folder 1-3)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 141 pp., and galley pages. The 3 plays are "Riverside Drive," "Old Saybrook" and "Central Park West."
      - Design sample layouts and galley pages, 2003-2004; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
        ANS by Random House; TMs with autograph corrections, 141 pp.
      - Galley proofs - 1st pass, 2003 October 1; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 216 pp.
      - Galley proofs - 2nd pass, 2003 October 23; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        TMs, 218 pp.
    - "Thus Ate Zarathustra", 2006; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp.; TMss, 4 and 5 pp.; TL and TMs with autograph corrections (original and facsimile), 4 and 13 pp. from "Roger" at The New Yorker (Xerox); TMs with autograph corrections, 5 pp., and AMs, 1 p., originally titled "Food for Thought," 5 pp.
    - "To Err is Human -- To Float, Divine", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      AMs written on legal notepad, 8 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 9 pp.
    - "Toward a Sub-Linear Mode of Film Criticism", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - "The Truth At Last" (Nixon Piece), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
      TMs, 3 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 2 pp.
    - "2001", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs (Xerox) of unfinished sketch, 6 pp.
    - "The UFO Menace", 1977-1980; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
      2 TMss with autograph corrections, 8 pp. each; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 9 pp.; TMs (Xerox), 8 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 1 p. (original) and 6 pp. (Xerox); original tear sheets from June 13, 1977 issue of The New Yorker; TL from their Fiction Department.
    - WAFP 98 [as yet untitled screenplay of Sweet and Lowdown (1999)], 1998 April 10; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs, bound copy of untitled screenplay, 94 pp. ("WAFP 98" = Woody Allen Fall Project 1998).
    - "What character in fiction would I most like to be?", 1984; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs, 1 p., and TL (Xerox) to Robert Harris of The New York Times.
    - What's New, Pussycat? (film), 1965; more than 4 folders (Folder 3-5)
      - Version 1, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 97 pp.
      - Version 2, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs (carbon) with autograph corrections, 126 pp.
      - Version 3, 1964; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
        TMs (Xerox, bound), 133 pp.
    - "The Whore of Medusa", 1974-1996; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
      TMs, 7 pp., and TL from The New Yorker's Fiction Dept.; original tear sheet from the Dec. 16, 1974 issue of The New Yorker; TL (facsimile), 3 pp.
    - "The Woody Allen Special", 1969; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy of television special, 66 pp.
    - "The Woody Allen Special", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
      Mixture of TMs pages with and without autograph corrections (original and Xerox).
    - "Writer's Block: Two One Act Plays", 2000 July 27; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
      TMs with autograph corrections of "New York" (46 pp.) and "New Milford" (33 pp.), later retitled "Riverside Drive" and "Old Saybrook," respectively.
    - "Writer's Block", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      AMs (incomplete draft) written on 2 legal notepads
    - "Writer's Block", 2002 September 6; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      TMs, 46 pp., of "New York" (later retitled "Riverside Drive")
    - "You Can't Go Home Again -- And Here's Why", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
    - Untitled Manuscripts, undated; 2.0 boxes
    - Untitled manuscript, circa 1960; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs, Act I (41 pp.) and Act II (40 pp.). Original typescript by Allen: first 2 acts of his first attempt at playwriting that was eventually abandoned.
    - Untitled screenplay: version 1, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound copy, 100 pp. Characters include: Doris, Natalie, Elvis, Ace, Monroe, Harvey, etc.
    - Untitled screenplay: version 2, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 84 pp. Characters include: Doris, Natalie, Elvis, Ace, Monroe, Harvey, etc.
    - Untitled screenplay manuscript, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 49 pp. Characters include: Harvey, Faye, Ben, Phil, Diane, Carol, Caroline.
    - Untitled screenplay (Part Four), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs, 41 pp. Characters include [007 James?] Bond, Hadley, Vesper.
    - Untitled screenplay (Second Draft), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs bound copy, 128 pp. Main character's name is Moses Rifkin.
    - Untitled screenplay manuscript, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy, 107 pp. Characters include Alva, David, Yale, Marty, Fred, etc.
    - Untitled story manuscript, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      AMs, 6 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp.
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs (incomplete), 8 pp. Characters include Word Babcock, Roxy Babcock, Sam Mbutu, etc.
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      Mixture of AMss (yellow sheets, 3 pp., and white sheets, 9 pp.) and TMs with autograph corrections (1 p.).
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      AMs (6 pp.) and TMs (7 pp.) featuring a character named Mersky.
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      AMs (yellow and white sheets), with characters named Leo, Alva, Chloe, etc.
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp. (bee as narrator)
    - Untitled manuscript, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
      TMss (carbon and Xerox copies), 6 pp., and AMs (Xerox), 6 pp.
    - Untitled manuscript, 2001; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs (Xerox), 5 pp. Original speech written after 9/11/01; a comic piece read by someone at AmfAR (The Foundation for AIDS Research) dinner.
    - Untitled compilation of One Liners, Bits, Monologues, Sketches, etc, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
      TMs, 196 pp.
    - Untitled Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      Mixture of TMss and AMss with autograph corrections
    - Untitled Miscellaneous manuscripts (Xeroxes), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
      Various AMss with autograph corrections
  - Subseries 5B: Correspondence, Copyrights, Agreements, etc, 1971-1997; 30.0 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence of Allen with television and radio stations, magazines and journals, and individuals. Included is correspondence with Orion Pictures, Random House, and Irwin Tenenbaum, Allen's attorney. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order and contain copyrights and agreements for books, films, plays, radio or television shows.
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Allen, Woody: Miscellaneous, 1987-1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - The American Film Institute, 1986; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - BBC TV, 1987; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - CBS, 1981-1986; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Barry Lee, Esq, 1982-1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Hackenbush Productions, Inc, 1976-1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Hallmark Cards, Inc, 1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Jones, G. Curtis, 1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Kiva Gallery, Boston, 1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Lucaire, Ed, 1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - MacMillan Publishing Co, 1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday Commission, 1987; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Motion Picture Association of America, Inc, 1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - The New York Review of Books, 1983-1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - The New Yorker Copyright Assignment for Stories, 1971-1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Orion Pictures Co, 1982-1986; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Portal Publications, 1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Random House, 1983-1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Rastar Television, Inc, 1981-1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Reader's Digest, 1984-1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Societe Nationale De Programme, 1980-1981; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Tenenbaum, Irwin J. (Allen's attorney), 1975-1986; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - United Nations, 1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Untitled Productions, Inc./Hackenbush Productions, Inc, 1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - USA Network, 1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Weekly Mail Film Festival, 1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - WNET, 1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Writer's Guild of America West, Inc, 1980-1988; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
  - Subseries 5C: Printed Material, 1964-2007; more than 4 folders (Folder 1-3)
    Consists of clippings, offprints, and Mere Anarchy: advance uncorrected proofs added in 2007.
    - Mere Anarchy: Advance Uncorrected Proofs, 2007; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      Copy of bound volume, 160 pp.
    - Offprints, 1974-1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      Issues of the Kenyon Review, The New Republic, and Tikkun
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1972; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      Clippings from Chicago Daily News' Panorama ("A Brief Explanation"), The New York Daily Column, and The New York Times ("A Brief, Yet Helpful, Guide to Civil Disobedience")
- Series 6: Additions, 1964 April 9-2004 May 26; 10.0 boxes
  Additions made in 2008.
  This series is arranged into two subseries: Film and Theater Scripts, and Video Cassettes and LP Records.
  - Subseries 6A: Film and Theater Scripts, 1968-2004 May 26; 8.0 boxes
    This subseries contains typed manuscripts and copies of many of Allen's film screenplays and theater scripts, the majority of which are bound. The folders are arranged in alphabetical order by title.
    - Alice (1990 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 106 pp.
    - Alice (1990 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 110 pp.
    - Annie Hall (1977 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs copy of screenplay, 131 pp.
    - Another Woman (1988 film), 1987; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 86 pp.
    - [ Bananas] Untitled Film Script by Woody Allen and Mickey Rose, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay (early version of Bananas), 66 pp.
    - [ Bananas] Untitled Film Script by Woody Allen and Mickey Rose, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - [ Bananas] El Weirdo: An Original Screenplay by Woody Allen and Mickey Rose, 1970 March 25; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay (early version of Bananas), Script no. 6, 116 pp.
    - [ Bananas] El Weirdo: An Original Screenplay by Woody Allen and Mickey Rose, 1970 March 25; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay (early version of Bananas), Script no. 98, 116 pp.
    - Bananas (1971 film), 1970; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs copy of Duplicate Lined Script with autograph corrections (Xerox and photostats), pp. 1-58. Script Supervisor Barbara Robinson's copy (part 1 of 2).
    - Bananas (1971 film), 1970; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs copy of script with autograph corrections (Xerox and photostats), pp. 58A-116. Script Supervisor Barbara Robinson's copy (part 2 of 2).
    - Broadway Danny Rose (1984 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 111 pp.
    - Celebrity (1998 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 123 pp., titled "Celebrities" on title page.
    - "Central Park West: A One Act Play", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of play, 69 pp.
    - Crimes and Misdemeanors (1989 film), 1988; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 100 pp. that was initially titled "Brothers."
    - Deconstructing Harry (1997 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 132 pp.
    - Deconstructing Harry (1997 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 138 pp.
    - Deconstructing Harry (1997 film), 1996-1997; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay with many colored pages of revisions (dated between July 15, 1996 and Jan. 20, 1997), 141 pp.
    - Don't Drink the Water (3-act play), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound copy of play, 123 pp.
    - Don't Drink the Water (1966 film), 1969; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay by R. S. Allen, Harvey Bullock and Marshall Brickman, based on Allen's play, 134 pp.
    - Don't Drink the Water (1966 film), 1994 March 14; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay with blue pages of revisions (dated March 28-29 and April 18, 1994), 104 pp.
    - Everyone Says I Love You (1996 film), 1995; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 124 pp. WAFP '95 (Woody Allen Fall Project 1995) written on title page.
    - Everyone Says I Love You (1996 film), 1995; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay with blue pages of revisions (dated Aug. 4, 1995), 133 pp.
    - Everything You've Always Wanted To Know About Sex... (1972 film), 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay
    - The Filmmaker (Tentative title) by Woody Allen and Marshall Brickman, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound screenplay, 100 pp., spelled "Filmaker" on the cover.
    - The Floating Light Bulb (two-act play), 1981 May 2; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs bound Performance copy of play, 93 pp.
    - The Floating Light Bulb (two-act play), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of a play
    - The Front by Walter Bernstein, 1975 August 13; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 121 pp. (pp. 119-199A revised Sept. 2, 1975)
    - The Front by Walter Bernstein, 1975; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs copy of screenplay, 121 pp., dated Aug. 13, 1975 on title page, with colored pages of revisions (dated Sept. 2 and 8, Nov. 18, and Dec. 8, 1975).
    - God, The Flag and Motherhood: A Comedy in Three Acts, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy of play, 126 pp.
    - God, The Flag and Motherhood, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs bound copy of play with autograph corrections (xerox)
    - Hannah and Her Sisters (1986 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 119 pp.
    - Interiors (1978 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound copy of shooting script, 98 pp.
    - Love and Death (1975 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 128 pp.
    - Manhattan (1979 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of shooting script, 107 pp.
    - Manhattan Murder Mystery (1993 film), 1992; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of first draft, 122 pp. WAFP '92.
    - Manhattan Murder Mystery (1993 film), 1992; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs bound copy of second draft, 123 pp. WAFP '92.
    - A Midsummer Night's Sex Comedy (1982 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 112 pp., titled "Summer Movie Project" on title page.
    - Mighty Aphrodite (1995 film), 1994; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 129 pp.
    - "New Milford" (one-act play), 2002-2003; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs of one act play, 35 pp., dated Oct. 21, 2002 with Jan. 24, 2003 revisions.
    - "Oedipus Wrecks" (from New York Stories, 1989 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 40 pp.
    - Play It Again, Sam (1972 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 100 pp.
    - Play It Again, Sam (1972 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - Play It Again, Sam (1972 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs bound copy of Shooting script, 106 pp.
    - The Purple Rose of Cairo (1985 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 117 pp., and Appendix, 6 pp.
    - Radio Days (1987 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs bound copy of screenplay, 122 pp.
    - "Riverside Drive" (one-act play), 2003 April 23-June 29; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs of one act play, 46 pp., originally titled "New York."
    - "A Second Hand Memory" (two-act play), 2004 May 26; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs of play, 93 pp.